Welcome to the Florida Department of Law
Enforcement. If you're having a life
threatening emergency, please hang up and
dial 911. Please select  oneof the
following options so that we can better
serve you.
For information on obtaining a criminal
history background check, please press 1.
If you have questions about stealing or
expunging a criminal history record, or
you want to check on the status of your
application, please press 2. If you have
questions about firearm background checks
or to check on the status of a firearm
related background check that has been
delayed or denied, please press 3. For
questions regarding officer certification
or training, press 4 to file a
complaint against the public official FDL
E member. Or learn how to file a
complaint against the law enforcement
officer. Press 5 for all other
inquiries.
Actually.
I had a call. Well, actually I want
to report a strong armed
robbery. Umm.
Several things. The police misconduct.
Also the Florida Department of Law
Enforcement because I've called before
and this call is being recorded.
I'm. I'm calling as a victim as
and as a member of the press, because
this will be published. We're gonna show
what happens. OK.
Alonzo, there was a case before.
I don't know. You might want to just
promote this up to a detective.
OK, so you said there was a robbery,
a strong armed robbery attempt. There's
been a. I've it's on
recording also I've got this. I got the
evidence on recording also a car
theft and it's all related to a
big old organized scheme to defraud in
the billions and that's where the be
dollars and y'all can call. Believe me I
can back all this up what I'm saying so
I'm prepared to talk to the investigator.
OK and. Are you able to put this in
writing before? Actually, I can
I but we've done that. I Let me get
your name and badge number. Also, Let's
just start off like that. I don't have a
badge number, but my name is Daria. OK,
RIA, fantastic. Thank you.
I don't know where we go. This is going
to be much. This is the biggest call that
you're going to get this week, probably
it's worth, it's worth in the billions of
dollars and it's all related to that.
OK, so I can provide you our e-mail
and you can send us any documentation.
No, we've we've done that before. I wanna
get. I wanna speak to a FDL E agent
with a badge number first and then he can
give me that because we tried that
before, OK?In the
NFL, the Inspector General's Office SLA
members worked hard to maintain the
highest standards in law enforcement,
developing and employing the latest
skills and techniques. FDLE has earned
triple accreditation by the National
Commission on Creditation for Law
Enforcement Agency, the Commission for
Florida Law Enforcement Accreditation,
and the American Society for Crime Lab
Directors. To learn more about the
accolades we've earned, visit our website
at FBLE dot state dot
FL. Dot US.
After your lease website, put public
safety information at your fingertips by
visiting us at www.
fdle. state. fl
. usyoucan obtain a criminal history
check for sexual offenders and predators.
Sign up to receive AMBER Alerts. Search
for I'm sorry, what was your name again?
I'll reserve that.
We've we've done this before. Alonzo
Green should be well, we've
we've done something with Alonzo Green
before. I'd like to speak to somebody, to
a real agent before I give my name.
OK.
Florida DNA Database is one of the
largest in the nation and has provided
more than 31,000 hits since its inception
in 1990.
Have you liked our Facebook page? FDL E
Facebook followers can view breaking
news, get notification when an Amber or
missing child alert is issued and stay up
to date with important cyber security
bulletin. We appreciate your call and
member will be available to assist you in
a moment.
Hey Inspector, my name is Lance
Mason and I've got a boatload of stuff
for you. If I could get an
e-mail I can. I can send
you the audio of a strong arm
robbery it's going to be related to t
heft of intellectual property, which I
can also prove we can just call over at
the State Board of Administration, which
I'll have jurisdiction over. I assume we
can we can test it out real quick and
it's it's billions of dollars. What I'm
talking about the the strong armed
robbery. It's on a recording. It's
related also at the theft of my
car and all kinds of
official misconduct and organized scheme
to defraud right there in Tallahassee.
At Florida State. See, I went to Florida
State. I'm a CPA, went to with the school
there. But we can get all into that and
I've got evidence just to back it up and
everything that we're saying here is
recorded and.
Having to do this to,
to flush it through, I mean we'll see.
You'll see that there should be a
complaint against Alonzo Green right now.
I mean there's like he's he was worried I
got him on a recording that's gonna be
that's gonna be Exhibit A because I've
said this stuff before to him
and he didn't want to hear it, but I've
got the recording and y'all can hear it.
So this, this is going to need to get
escalated up, I'm certain of it.
If I could get an e-mail where
you know not the general comments
e-mail but the specific
person so that there can be a chain of
custody on this because he he
was sent out there to to bury
the case to not do anything and that's
what that's why the that's the nature of
why I picked 5 on the dial right there to
go to internal. This should be an
internal affairs and higher than the
issue go up to the governor's office. But
you'll see all that as I present the
evidence.
OK, First things first.
I do not give permission to be recorded.
So if you are recording me, I do request
that you stop recording me. I don't give
permission or consent for you to record
me. Fair enough, I can do that.
OK. And also and now
we do have a e-mail address that we
use to facilitate you know
information such as this and what happens
is when it goes into this e-mail is
forwarded to the appropriate.
Let me get your e-mail address.  I've
already I've already I've that's that's I
I want a so your
name. You're
answering to the public, by the way. This
is I I'm trying to give you information.
If you want to send out the information,
I'm trying to give you a, you know, a way
to look at it.
We need to look at it. So if you're ready
to copy the e-mail address,  isit? Is
that going to be a specific person?
We have to get the one that made this.
Right now, if you're ready to come back.
There. I'll tell you what let me give
you, let me give you my Facebook
account and y'all go.
If you have information that you just
said it was urgent, I did. Did I say hey,
by the way, I'm I'm not you're answering
to the public here. I'm recording either
way so.
This call because I did ask you not to
record me. Well, for what reason do you
not want to be recorded?
But don't you you're you're acting in a
you're but you're acting.
Not that. Well, let's let's listen to
young one. I want to hear what you're
saying. What's your name
again?
But you're a you're a public official.
You're answering to the public here, You
don't have a right to privacy. No, I'm
not you. You don't have a right. You
don't have a expectation of privacy, do
you?You do You have it.
But you're not. You're acting as an
agent, telling you again, if you're
recording me, I do not.
I do not.
That seems, but you don't have an
expectation of privacy.
What's your name again?
Again. So before we go further, I'm
getting a Philly. I'm not giving you
this. OK, well, what's your name again?
That's fair enough. What's your name?
Recording me? No.
What's your name? What is your name? What
is your name and badge number?What is
your name and badge number? I can give
you my last name. What's your What's your
badge number?
You don't have an expectation of privacy.
OK.
No, I'm trying to. I'm trying to put
evidence.
Ohh it is.
#4ohh yes.
Well, go ahead. I would
not. I'm not. I'm not
antagonist.
When you're ready to submit some
information, give us a call back and
we'll give you the information.
That's all I'm trying to do, but it seems
like you're getting very secretive.